I love you yuri
I hope we stay together forever and ever
Why so sudden my love?
Of course we’ll stay together and forever
I love you too
Ikaw talaga ah
(*Nag lalandian ang mga juding*)
Ikaw ah
Where's that boy
Why isn’t this boy answering?!
I swear if he’s with that Keifer guy again-
ikaw ah
Wait lang wait lang
Hi mom!
Yes yes yes I’m going home, don't worry
Yuri!
Are you with that Keifer guy again?
I swear,
go home right now.
I don’t want you hanging out with that person.
He’s influencing you badly!
But Mom! I thought we'd already talked about this.
I love him okay?
I don’t wanna hear your scolding anymore.
I’m old enough to decide for myself and you know that.
Go home at once!
Whats that about?
*Sighs*
Its my mom
Dont worry about it
But I really need to go home
It’s okay I understand. I’ll walk you back home.
No no no its ok
I'l- i'll walk alone
Pretty sure my mom doesn’t even want to see you anymore
sorry, I’m very sorry.
Ok walk safe
Call me once you got home okay?
Bye!
(Yuri's House)
(knocks)
I'm Home
Where have you been? I’ve been worried sick-
Mom Just-
Don't be over dramatic okay?
(*Furious*) Are you with that Keifer again?
Yes i am
But
What is it to you?
How many times do I need to say and repeat it?!
Your relationship with Keifer is a sin!
It’s a sin against God’s eyes!
I get what your trying to say mom!
You kept telling it to me every single time
But that doesn't change the fact
That i still love Him!
(*Shocked*) Are you hearing yourself right now?!
Go to your room!
You’re grounded from now on!
What!?
But!?
(*Speechless*)
(*kicked the wall*)
(*Keifer's House*)
Dad?
I'm Home
Son! Go ahead and eat first. I’m gonna take a nap since I have a duty later.
Yes Keifer
May i have your advice
Yes, What is it? Something bothering you?
Yes
Is it love life?
Its about that "Guy"
That Guy" the one that you have telling me
A million times already
Yes
His mother is against our relationship.
Well may i know why?
His mom is a religious person
And
And she says that it is a sin
Uh huh…
Well son
in this world
Everyone has a different perspectives and beliefs
You can’t really change someone's mindset, right?
I get your point dad
But its her own  beliefs
And
I think that She should not force on us.
And We are old enough, to make our own decisions
Right?
Son,  I also get your point. But hear me out. You know that I support both you and Yuri, right?
Yes
Right. I’m not defending Yuri’s mother, but she has the right to be against your relationship.
You’ve mentioned that she is a religious person, so what can you expect?
They believe that God only created men and women. A man is only for women, and women is only for men
Just like what Genesis 1:27 says
Dad
I dont get your point
I'm a human i have feelings
I love yuri
I love Him
No because of His gender
But
Because of
For who He is
Do you get me?
I get your side son
But lets face reality
Like what I’ve said earlier, you can’t force your belief on someone else.
Everyone has a different perspective and belief's.
What matters is that we respect each other, right?
Yes dad
but
I dont think that
I'll-  I can keep my distance from him
You know?
His Mom wants us to break up and never associate again!
Give it a time son
Don’t rush in making decisions
I know that you’ll be able to figure it out
Plus, you could talk to me when you need help, right?
*sigh*
Yes dad
Thank you
(*At the School*)
Hey Keifer!
I haven’t seen you and Yuri around lately! What’s up?
Uhh
Nothing really
Have you heard anything about Yuri?
Well, I haven’t seen him much except when we have classes together.
Im worried sick
He hasn't chatted me or called me yet
Since yesterday
oh, actually
earlier
I peeked at his phone and i saw his mother's messages
Huh!?
Yeah
It seems like his mother is trying to separate  you both.
What?!
Yeah, and his been grounded
I need to talk to him
Alright But
Before you talk to him
Can i give you a peice of advice
okay sure
So
You know that i support you both right?
And im a witness with your relationship
Yes
And
It'll be hard for you so
You should be ready
Yeah
I know that wayn
Ah
A part of me is tired of
Chasing Him
And avoiding his mother at all times
And i just want
Both of us to express our love
Thats why im telling you
That you should be strong
You should be strong for your relationship
For you and for yuri too!
So if you ever need me just call me okay?
Okay. thank you wayn bye!
Thank you
(*The Reunion*)
Excuse me Sir, can you please help me with this-
Yes Ma’am, what can I do for you?
Alejandro?!
Is that really you??
Well, if it isn't Florence. How have you been?
It’s been years since our last reunion!
Oh please, save that conversation of yours later.
I didn’t expect you to be a lawyer.
Well, I just did. So, what can I do for you?
I want to file a restraining order.
A restraining order?
Is someone bothering or threatening you?
No, it’s not for me. It’s for my son.
Really? so is there someone who's threatening your son?
Well, he has this “boyfriend” of his.
I don’t want them associating with each other!
I’m sorry? His BOYFRIEND?
Can you tell me exactly why you want to file a restraining order against him?
Do you really need the details? I just want him gone from my son's life!
I don’t want them associating with each other!
I’m sorry Florence, but if you don’t give me a specific reason
I can not help you with this What even is his name?
His name is Keifer. Keifer Velvetine
What?! Thats my son
Your son? What? No way…
He is! My one and only Keifer Velvetine! So you’re that boyfriend’s mother he’s been talking about!
What?
What mother are you talking about?
You’re the mother of his boyfriend! Yuri! Yuri Haruka!
No way… So why aren’t you trying to separate them both! You knew about their relationship!
Alright, let’s get back why you are here in the first place.
you want to get a restraining order for your son against his boyfriend?  No, I can not help you with tat.
What? What do you mean by that?
You’re a lawyer aren’t you? What’s the purpose of your job if you’re not able to help me?
Don’t you know that you could have serious consequences when you’re trying to file a restraining order without valid reason?
This is considered as an abuse of the legal system!
Which can result in penalties and even criminal charges!
This is absurd!
Florence, I know that you have a strong relationship towards God
And you know that I respect that, but please, let the kids be happy. They can decide for themselves!
Are you even hearing yourself right now, Alejandro?!
Florence, please calm down! Think about it!
(*The break up*)
Hey
Yuri?
uy!
Whats wrong?
Keifer
I have something to tell you
What?
Tell me!
We-
We need to break up
What!?
Why?
Its just
This is all wrong
Keifer
Huh?
What wrong?
I'm Tired
Tired!
If your tired
Why wont you fight for our relationship
I have tried
Tried multiple times
Yet nothing changes
Its draining all my life
I cant keep up with you anymore
I respect your desicion
Okay
Lets break up then
Thank you
Thank you keifer
I hope- , I hope you dont forget me
I stil llove you
Welcome everyone! to the Highschool Reunion of Batch 2013-2014!
I hope everyone has a good time here!
Yuri?
Keifer?